Guide to the Elayne Zalis video studies archive, [circa 1979-1997].
Zalis, Elayne video studies archive
- Series III. Alphabetic Subject Files
  - Hallwalls (feminism and surveillance) (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - “Video Witness Festival of New Journalism,” poster and calendar, February 1990 (2 copies)
  - Hampshire College, Amherst, MA (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Spring 1989 Course Guide
  - Hawaii International Film Festival (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Information packet including submission application and 1989 festival programs / schedules. Includes original mailing envelope.
  - Heritage Cable (Public Access) (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Flowcharts and checklists for script development process, treatment for a story
  - Heritage Cable (Public Access) (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Flowcharts and checklists for script development process, treatment for a story
  - Kathy High--videomaker, journal editor (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - “Feeling the Faults: Confronting dis-ease throught the mediated body,” program newsletter and schedule
    - Media Matters Vol. 8 no. 5, September-October 1990
  - High Performance (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Subscription information and renewal form. Include original mailing envelope
  - Holography (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - “The Holo-Gram,” First-Half, 1989
    - “The Holo-Gram,” Second-Half, 1989Includes letter from editor Frank DeFreitas and original mailing envelope.
    - Information on holographic plates, Towne Laboratories Inc. Includes sales engineer business card and original mailing envelope. 1989
    - Postcard advertising event “Equus / Underwater,” by Nancy Gorglione and Greg Cherry, Museum of Holography, Chicago, 1989
  - Horror--Books (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Mark V. Ziesing newsletter No. 82, August 1989
    - Ziesing newsletter No. 79
    - Ziesing newsletter No. 81, June 1989
    - Ziesing newsletter No. 83
    - Mark V. Ziesing book catalog and newsletter No. 84
  - How(ever) (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - One page from Vol. 5 no. 2, January 1989
  - How(ever) journal (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - “How(ever)” Vol. 6 no. 1, January 1990
  - Image Film/Video Center, Atlanta (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - “Image—news about independent film and video,” newsletter, April 1987
  - Institute for Media Analysis (IMA) (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - “Friends of IMA: Post=Conference News from the Institute for Media Analysis, Inc.,” newsletter, February 1989
    - “Packaging the Contras: A Case of CIA disinformation,” by Edgar Chamorro, Institute for Media Analysis, Inc. Monograph Series No. 2, 1987. Includes original mailing envelope.
  - International Television Association (ITVA) (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - “ITVA Chicago Chapter News,” newsletter, May 1990. Includes original mailing envelope with membership information and application.
    - “The 8th Annual Golden Slate Awards, 1989” event invitation.
    - Letter from Eric Silverstein, membership coordinator, December 1988
    - Membership information pamphlet
    - Mailing envelope, December 1988, with Zalis’ scribbles
    - Promotional postcard and invitation to “There is more to this than meets the mind,” video and performance art event, 1989
    - “Entry kit, 23rd Annual ITVA Video Festival,” 1990
    - International Television Association informational pamphlet
  - Intermedia Arts Minnesota (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - “The Techno’Logical Imagination: Machines in the Garden of Art,” symposium program, November 1989
    - Promotional postcard for video release by Deb Wallwork
    - “Intermedia Arts Minnesota,” newsletter, Vol. 17 no. 3, Spring 1990(2 copies), includes listing of Film in the Cities and Intermedia Arts Minnesota listing of courses, Winter quarter 1988-1989
    - “Intermedia Arts Minnesota,” newsletter, Vol. 16 no. 2, Winter 1989(2 copies)
    - “Intermedia Arts Minnesota,” newsletter, Vol. 17 no. 1, Fall 1989
    - Informational brochure, includes donation information and form, three versions, dates uncertain
    - “Changing Channels,” Spring schedule UC Video, April-June 1987
    - UC Video, packet of information about services, collaboration, organization mission, equipment rental
    - Letter to Zalis from Al Kosters, director of artist programs, August 23, 1989
    - Video catalog, date uncertain
  - Iowa Artists (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Promotional card and invitation, “Moment of Silence,” by Toma Longinovic, event hosted by Iowa International Writing Program, date uncertain
    - “Crossing Over: Video, Criticism, Theory,” symposium program, 1988
    - “The Landing Party,” party invitation
    - “Choice,” photocopied book of photographs of a women’s march in Washington, DC. Photos by Normal, autographed to Zalis by the artist.
    - Booklet of writings by Bonnie Sparling and Rita ResPense
    - “5 from the vault, Volume 1—the Iowa Collection,” photocopied program for video series, 1988
    - “Vampire of the Banalities,” Matthew Wills, photocopied book review
    - Computer images, 2 pages
    - Letter regarding Laurie Anderson performance at Hancher Auditorium, February 9, 1990
    - Newspaper article regarding “Poetry TV,” March 9, 1990
    - Postcard to Zalis
    - “Fax Art: Its History and Applications,” poster for lecture by Harry Heyink, November 1990
  - Journals – Misc (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Subscription information for Third Text, date uncertain
    - MIT Press Journals, catalog 1988
    - Johns Hopkins University Press, Journals, 1988
    - Mailing envelope from Aperture, contents uncertain, July 1990
    - Poster advertising Routledge Book Week, date uncertain
    - “Strategies: A Journal of theory, culture and politics,” Call for Papers on the topic of “Marx after Elvis: The Politics of Popular Culture,” 1990
    - “Strategies: A Journal of theory, culture and politics,” subscription and ordering information. Includes original mailing envelope, June 1990
    - “Architecture Art Design,” book catalog, MIT press, 1988. Includes note on available titles not included in catalog.
  - Kansas City Art Institute (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Packet of information on “The Elegant Merging,” 1988 exhibit. Includes exhibition information from Utah Media Arts Center, Salt Lake Art Center, and Kansas City Art Institute
    - Packet of information on “The Elegant Merging,” including press release from Kansas City Art Institute and 8 photographic slides of exhibit
  - Mary Kelly (Interim, LBMA and New Museum, NY) (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Letter to Zalis regarding Kelley’s “Interim,” from Abigail Smith, Assistant Administrator of the New Museum of Contemporary Art, 20 March 1990
    - Program for symposium “Subjects of History,” held in connection with “Interim” exhibition at the New Museum, March 10, 1990
    - Program for “Interim Part I: Corpus,” at Los Angeles Contemporary Exhibitions
  - The Kitchen: Center for Video, Music Dance, Performance & Film, NY (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - ‘The Kitchen Video Distribution Program New Acquisitions’
    - ‘Video Distribution Price list,’ ’88-’89
    - ‘The Kitchen Video Distribution Title List,’ March, 1989
    - ‘The Kitchen’ publication, no date
    - Folder of assorted news publications
  - Lookout Lesbian and Gay Video Festival ‘90, Toronto (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - ‘Lookout Lesbian and Gay Video Festival ‘90’, Program with contact info
    - Festival Program
    - Festival Poster
  - Long Beach Museum of Art, CA (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Relyea, Lane. Remembrances of Things Past: collected writings and exhibition catalogue, Long Beach Museum of Art 1986. Curator: Connie Fitzsimons
    - 2x- ‘Planes of Memory’ Catalogue, Curated by Jacqueline Kain, 1988
    - ‘Shirley Clarke in Retrospect: selected video and film 1953-1958’. 1987
    - Art rental/ sales gallery publication. ‘Introductions: 1989-1990’
    - ‘Open Channels’ Publications, II, IV
    - ‘Video: 1984’ Publication
    - 1989 Television Production Grant Program application and information
    - Long Beach Museum of Art Cable Programming Schedule, no date
    - Various press releases
    - LBMA Video Newsletter, Spring 1987
    - ‘Comment’ publication, 1983
    - 2 postcards
    - Museum membership application
  - Long Beach Museum of Art, CA (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - LBMA Video folder, various museum handouts and publications
  - Los Angeles Contemporary Exhibitions (LACE) (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - 2 newsprint publications, 1987
  - Los Angeles Festival (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Program and ticket information
    - ‘Hungers,’ Ed Emshwiller & Morton Subotnick, Bio/statement, 1987
  - Los Angeles Arts – Fringe Festival (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Fringe news publications and reviews from: Los Angeles Times, L.A. Downtown News, and L.A. Weekly
    - Fringe Festival catalogue, Los Angeles, 1988
  - MacArthur Library John D. and Catherine T. MacArthur Foundation (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Macarthur public library video collection catalogue
    - ‘Video Classics’ Publication
  - Macintosh – Superpaint manual (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - MacPaint Manual
  - Mail Art (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Various mail art projects including: ‘Schism #15’, ed. Janet Janet ‘Ready Mail’, Pascal Lenoir Mutant Musick Distribution, 1987, Berlin. Arte Postale!, Italy Constrictor Magazines, Italy Rutkovsky, Paul. Postcard Gunderloy, Michael, Rensselaer, NY. Anti-authoritarians Anonymous- Various Posters. Eugene, Oregon. Luna Bisonte Prods, Catalog No. 12, 1987 Galantai- Artpool Budapest, Hungary
  - Victor Mosayesva, Jr., Videomaker (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - (see Intermedia Arts Catalog and Native American Video) (empty folder)
  - Media Alliance, NY (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Media Matters Newsletters: Vol.8, No.3 1990. Vol.7, No.1 1989, Vol. 8, No.6 1990.
    - Guidelines and Policies
  - Media Alliance/ New York, Directory of Members 1990 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Media Network: Alternative Media Information Center, NY (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Information and ordering information
  - Metropolitan Museum of Art / J. Paul Getty Trust: Program for Art on Film (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Program for Art on Film information/ press release
    - Films on Art Bibliography
  - Miami Design Preservation League (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - ‘Art Deco’ pamphlet
  - Miami – Journal of Decorative and Propaganda Arts (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - The Journal of Decorative and Propaganda Arts, Fall 1988. Ed. Pamela Johnson
  - Miller, Branda, videomaker and curator (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - ‘Surveillance: An Exhibition of Video, Photography, Installations’ catalogue’ photocopy, 1987. Cur. Branda Miller: video, installations, Deborah Irmas: Photography.
  - Millennium Film Workshop, Inc. NY (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - 25th Anniversary: Fall Series 1990 Programs
  - Misc. (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Miscellaneous pamphlets and papers
  - MTV Networks (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Various MTV Networks press releases (~1979-1985) including MTV, Nickelodeon, ‘Remote Control’, and ‘Double Dare’
    - Various articles about MTV Networks
    - Black and white glossy photograph from ‘Remote Control’
  - 8th Biennial John Muir Medical Film Festival, Walnut Creek, CA- 1990 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Competition fact sheet
    - Call for entries publication
    - Catalog of entries
  - Museum of the American Indian Film and Video Center, NY (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Informational pamphlet
    - ‘Amazon Week, Reflecting on the Brazilian Rainforest: a dialogue with the insiders’ poster, 1990
  - Museum of Broadcast Communications at River City, Chicago (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Pamphlet
  - Long Beach Museum of Art, CA (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Museum of Broadcasting, NY (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Screening schedules- 1989
    - Profile publication
  - Museum of Contemporary Art, Chicago (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - 2 Mailings with ‘Contemporary Art Store’ posters
  - Museum of Modern Art, NY (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - “From Sound Stage To Strong, Silent Museum,” The New York Times, 1989
    - ‘Television by Godard Miéville,’ pamphlet, Dist by Electronic Arts Intermix, no date.
    - Video Supplement: 1985 Circulating Video Library
    - ‘Video at the Museum of Modern Art’ Press release, no date
    - ‘Video and Language,’ Barbara London. 1989 press release and schedule.
    - ‘Selections from the Video Study Collection: 1968-97.’ 1987 press release.
    - Circulating Film Library, film descriptions
    - ‘New Video: Japan’ poster, 1986
    - ‘Readings on Video: a resource list” 1987
    - ‘VIDEO: Video for Libraries and Media Centers’
    - ‘New Video: Japan’ catalogue publication, 1985
  - Museum of the Moving Image, Queens, NY (Box ??, Folder ??)
  - National Alliance of Media Arts Centers (NAMAC)- 1990 Member Directory (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - MAIN (Media Arts Information Network) Travel Sheet, September 1990
    - 1990 Member Directory
  - National Alliance of Media Arts (NAMAC)- Newsletters, Media Arts (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - ‘The Unblinking Eye: Effecting Change in the 90s’ 10th Anniversary Conference, 1990. Schedule and postcard.
    - ‘NAMAC Memo to the Field: Final Chance to Save the NEA,’ no date.
    - ‘MEDIA ARTS’ Spring/Summer 1990. Volume 2, Issue 7.
    - ‘MEDIA ARTS’ Winter/Spring 1990. Vol 2, Issues 5 and 6.
    - ‘MEDIA ARTS’ Summer/Fall 1987. Vol.2 Issue 3.
    - ‘MEDIA ARTS’ Spring/Summer 1989, Vol. 2, Issue 4.
    - July 16, 1990 Press release
    - Membership application
  - 48 National Cable Network Directory (Natl. Cable TV Assoc.) D.C. (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - National Cable Network Directory. March/April 1989
  - National Center for Film and Video Preservation 1989 (F/TAAC Clippings Packets) (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Report on the National Archives and Records Administration (NARA) Advisory committee meeting on the Preservation of Video Recordings, July 1987
    - ‘Preservation, Deterioration and Restoration of Recording Tape’ Steven Smolian, 1988. “Audio Preservation: A Planning Study” submission to the ARSC Journal for publication, 9/88
    - ‘Maximizing the Life of your Videocassette Tape’ Jim Wheeler, Apr 11, 1985. 6 photocopied articles on preservation of tape and video
    - NARA Advisory Committee on Preservation Ad Hoc Subcommittee on Preservation of Video Recordings, July 28-29, Washington D.C. photocopied minutes.
  - National Center for Film and Video Preservation F/TAAC – Fall 1990 Newsletter and Clippings (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - F/TAAC Newsletter, Vol.3 No.2 (Issue No. 10), Fall 1990
    - Fall 1990 clippings packet with index
  - National Center for Film and Video Preservation F/TAAC1989 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Spring 1990 Clippings Packet with Index
    - Summer 1990 Clippings Packet with Index Part 1
    - Summer 1990 Clippings Packet with Index Part 2
    - F/TAAC Newsletter, Vol. 3 No.1 (Issue No. 9)
    - F/TAAC Newsletter, Vol. 2 No.3 (Issue No. 7)
    - F/TAAC Newsletter, Vol. 2 No.4 (Issue No. 8)
  - National Center for Film and Video Preservation (F/TAAC Newsletters and Clippings) 1989 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - F/TAAC Newsletter Vol. 2 No. 2 (Issue No. 6)
    - FAAC/TAAC description and advisory committee membership list
    - Fall 19891989 Clippings Packet and Index
    - Summer 19891989 Clippings Packet and Index
  - National Center for Film and Video Preservation F/TAAC (AFI, L.A.) 1989 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - F/TAAC Advisory Committee Meeting, Miami, FL 1989 Information
    - AMIA Clippings Packet (Fall 1991-Winter 1992)
    - AMIA Newsletter, Fall 1991/Winter 1992
  - National Educational Film and Video Festival 1990, Oakland, Cali. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - 20th Anniversary Publication
    - 1989 Catalog
  - National Endowment for the Arts (NEA) (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - “Guide to the National Endowment for the Arts,” April 1987
  - National Federation of Local Cable Programmers (NFLCP) (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Membership promotional brochures
    - Publications and Videotapes list
    - Photocopied News articles
    - NFLCP Advocate 1990 National Convention informational/entry packet
    - 13th Annual Hometown USA Video Festival, 1990 information and entry form
  - National Geographic Video (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Small video catalog, 1987
  - National Sound and Communications Association (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - ‘Electronic Contracting’ Newsletter, February/March, 1990
    - Unopened envelope from NSCA
  - National Video Resources (NVR) (non-profit resource center) (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - ‘News from NVR’, 1990
    - ‘NVR Reports’, Issue # 1, Fall 1990
  - Native American Video (Box 6, Folder 7)
    See also Victor Masayesva, Jr.
    - “Afterimage”, Volume 17 Number 6, January 1990
  - Nebraska Videodisc Design / Production Group (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Informational packet
    - Symposium Publication: “A Decade of Development” May 21-24, 1990
  - New Museum of Contemporary Art, NY (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Tenth Anniversary Publication, 1977-1987
    - The New Museum of Contemporary Art Publications List, July 1987
    - “Stay Tuned” exhibition catalog, cur. Ned Rifkin. 1987
    - New Museum Zalis Invoice, July 22, 1997
  - New Orleans Video Access Center (NOVAC) (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Pamphlets
  - New York Expo of Short Film and Video (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - 1990 Program
  - New York Expo of Short Film and Video (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Flier
  - New York Video- Monday/Wednesday/Friday Video Club (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Membership Agreement, 1987
    - June 25,1987 Press release
    - M/W/F Catalog with prices
  - The 90’s (Chicago) (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - ‘The 90’s’ Newsletter, Summer/Fall 1990
    - Center for New Television course list
    - “The 90’s” Series press release, November 5, 1989
    - ‘The 90’s’ Program Summaries
    - Video catalog
  - Niteclub Video S.F. (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Publication and listing
  - Olander, William (critic, curator) (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Art & Social Change, U.S.A. Oberlin College Bulletin Volume XL, Number 2, 1982-1983
  - Pacific Film Archive, UC Berkeley (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - January 1989 Calendar
    - Pamphlet
    - Tribute to Italian actress Anna Magnani program
  - Oregon Art Institute – Northwest Film and Video Festival Portland (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Festival Poster, November 1988
    - ‘Film’ May/June 1990
    - Festival Poster, 1990
    - ‘Film’ Dec/Jan/Feb 1990
    - 1990 Festival Program
  - Oregon Art Institute – Northwest Film and Video Festival II (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - 1990 Festival schedule
    - ‘Film’ March/April 1990
    - ‘Film’ Dec/Jan/Feb 1990
    - ‘Film’ Summer 1989
    - ‘Film’ Jan/Feb 1989
    - ‘Film’ Sep/Oct/Nov 1989
    - ‘Film’ Spring 1988
    - ‘Film’ Fall 1987
    - ‘Film’ Summer 1987
    - 1988Festival schedule
    - ‘Animator’ Number 42, Winter 1988
    - ‘Animator’ Number 39, Fall 1986
    - ‘Animator’ Number 40, Spring 1987
    - ‘Animator’ Number 41, Fall 1987
  - Oryx Press (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Catalog of publications, 1986-1987
  - Pacific Arts Video (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Catalog
    - Promotional posters
  - Paper Tiger Television (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - “Paper Tiger Television” DeeDee Halleck
    - CAT*A*LOG
    - Publication, 1987
  - Pittsburgh Filmmakers: The Media Arts Center (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Promotional pamphlets
    - Class schedule, Fall 1990
  - Political Video – New Journalism (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - ‘Video Witnesses: Festival of New Journalism’ Hallwalls Contemporary Art Center, Buffalo, 1990
    - ‘A Tool, A Weapon, A Witness: The New Video News Crews’ Organized by Mindy Faber, Randolph Street Gallery, Chicago 1990
    - Video Witnesses Festival schedule
    - Video Witnesses Poster, 1990
  - Public Television (Iowa) (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Membership donation envelope
    - “Sizzlin’ Series,” photocopied article from Advance, July 1990 (4-5)
    - “Summer Variety,” photocopied article from Advance, June 1990 (6-7)
    - “July Program Schedule,” photocopied from Advance, July 1990 (11)
    - Advance August 1990 (Iowa Public Television newsletter)
  - Public Access TV – general (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Note from Mary Avalon, project coordinator, Rose City Community Television
    - Studio, Portland Oregon
  - Public Television – WGBH (Boston) The American Experience (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Submission guidelines for programs or proposals for The American Experience, 1990
  - Public Television – Thirteen / WNET (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Independent Focus ’91 call for entries, 1991
  - Punk Video – general (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Catalog of titles and merchandise. One page.
  - Publishers (Books) (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - “Culture, Media, Film,” Publisher catalog, Routledge, 1990
  - Radio (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - “Wireless,” public radio gift catalog, Fall/Winter 1990
    - “New Dimensions Radio,” newsletter, catalog, and donation envelope, 1988
    - “The NPR Cassette Catalog,” 1988
    - National Public Radio newsletter and catalog, date uncertain.
  - Radio Pacifica Radio Archive (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - “Pacifica Radio Archive Cassette Catalogue,” 1987
  - Randolph Street Gallery, Chicago P-Form (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - “P-Form: Performance Art News,” Vol. 2, no. 3, Summer 1987
    - Letter from Dani Kopoulos, the Randolph St. Gallery, 1987
    - “Visual Narrative / New Chicago Video,” exhibition review, Jamirte Trott, photocopied from P-Form, 1987
    - P-Form Calendar, and “HEAT and WATER,” poem by Matthew Buckingham. One page, 2-sided page.
  - Rankin, Scott (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Notes from Scott Rankin, August1986, Iowa City
    - “Video and Language Video as Langauge,” gallery guide from exhibit at LACE, curated by Scott Rankin. 2 copies.
  - Rochester Institute of Technology, American Video Institute (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - “RIT The American Video Institute and Rochester Institute of Technology,” promotional pamphlet, 1986
    - Packet of articles involving the AVI, 9 pp. photocopied
    - “News from Philosophical Library,” advertisement for Communicaiton: The Living End, by John A. Ciampa
    - Photocopied information packet: “History of AVI,” 6 pp.
  - Rocky Mountain Film Center (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Informational pamphlet and course listings, 1990
  - Rubnitz, Tom --videomaker (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - “Filming for a Different Drummer,” article by Hilton Als, LIFE, source unknown.
  - SF Camerawork, San Francisco (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - SF Camerawork Gallery exhibition announcement, Sylvia Plachey and Michael Spano, 1987-1988
    - Postcard announcement of exhibition, James D. Phelan Art Award in Photography, 1987-1988, winners Shari Lamanet, Reagan Louie, Adrienne Salinger.
  - San Francisco Cinematheque (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Packet of information, including note from Michelle Sabol, exhibition assistant, invoice, Summer 1990 calendar and newsletter, mission statement, and press release.
    - “Program Notes and Index,” 1989
    - “San Francisco Cinematheque 1990 Program Notes"
  - San Francisco International Film Festival (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Note from Brian Gordon, competition coordinator, 1990
    - San Francisco International Film Festival Golden Gate Awards entry form, 1990
    - “33rd San Francisco International Film Festival” program guide, 1990 (2 copies)
    - San Francisco International Film Festival Golden Gate Awards entry form, 1991
  - San Francisco International Video Festival (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Press release regarding juried selection and winners of the 1986 San Francisco International Video Festival. 4 pages.
  - Santa Cruz, UC – Video Program (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - “Perspective: University of California Extension, Santa Cruz,” program description and course catalog, Fall 1990
    - “University of California Extension Media Center Film and Video Catalog, 1989
    - “The Video Arts,” University of California Extension, Santa Cruz, program description, Summer 1990
  - Satellite Communications for Learning (SCOLA) Omaha, Nebraska (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - SCOLA information brochure
    - “SCOLA Global” newsletter, May 1988
    - Packet of photocopied articles about satellite broadcasting and communications (19pp, some double-sided)